

# Natalya Sentemova

Frontend developer

Address: Armenia, Gyumri

**Phone:** +3043068596

Email: ns.sent@yandex.ru

Website: resume

Telegram: https://t.me/TaliSent

LinkedIn <u>myLinkedIn</u>

Frontend developer with about 3 years of experience. Skilled at React.js, Typescript, HTML & CSS, Figma. Worked in a team of specialists and as a sole developer on 6 very different projects in total. Quickly learn all the required technologies. Interested in relocation. Most often described by collegues as "nice to communicate with":)

#### Resume

#### **Employment**

Oct 2019 - Present - Cinimex

Moscow

Frontend developer

- developed web applications with React.js, Redux, TypeScript, Node.js, Jest, Thrifts, Sass, BEM, Styled Components, material-ui, etc.
- Jira & Git, Kibana, Maraphon

Developed a bank application that allows user to configure, watch in PDF and sign documents.

# Aug 2018 — May 2019 - AT Consulting

Moscow

SQL developer

• writed SQL queries for widgets and printed forms

Developed a 30-pages printed form with around 50 SQL queries, each with complex business logic.

## Aug 2018 — May 2019 - AT Consulting

Moscow

**QA** Engineer

- tested widgets, written in Java + SQL
- worked with databases and created test data (MySQL)
- provided automation testing support

Fixed critical bugs in autotests .

Education		Web-dev Skills
2012 – 2018 — Moscow State University Bachelor of Physics	Moscow	React
Predicted electron fluxes with neural networks, data proccesed with Python and Numpy		Typescript
2021 - Codeacademy Learn React Course	Online	Vanilla Js
2021 - Codeacademy Learn React Part II Course	Online	Figma
2021 — Zar Zakcharov	Online	HTML
React Maraphon		CSS
A month of intense work on a card game.		

### Hobby

Drawing, TRPGs, singing, jiu jitsu. Studying:)